{
    "id": "c17241218fc44da3acbc7a8aebedf41a",
    "title": "Irregular Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have …………………………….. twelve eggs.",
            "description": "Bought is the past participle form of buy.",
            "answers": [
                "buyed",
                "bought",
                "buy"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ………………………….. the violin?",
            "description": "Brought is the past participle form of bring. ",
            "answers": [
                "bring",
                "bringed",
                "brought"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………….. there motionless.",
            "description": "Lay is the past tense of lie. ",
            "answers": [
                "lied",
                "lain",
                "lay"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Much water has …………………………. under the bridge.",
            "description": "Flowed is the past participle of flow. ",
            "answers": [
                "flowed",
                "flew",
                "flown"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly he ………………………….. from his seat.",
            "description": "Rose is the past participle of rise. ",
            "answers": [
                "rised",
                "rose",
                "risen"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The injured person was ………………………………. to hospital.",
            "description": "Taken is the past participle of take. ",
            "answers": [
                "take",
                "took",
                "taked",
                "taken"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………… a black shirt.",
            "description": "Wore is the past tense of wear.",
            "answers": [
                "wear",
                "wore",
                "worn"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………………. her hand.",
            "description": "Rise is intransitive. Raise is transitive. Raised is the past simple form of raise. ",
            "answers": [
                "raise",
                "rised",
                "raised",
                "rose"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Who …………………………….. juice on the carpet?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "spilled",
                "spilt",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The ship ………………………….. to the bottom.",
            "description": "Sank is the past simple form of sink.",
            "answers": [
                "sinked",
                "sank",
                "sunk"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was …………………………….. some photographs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "showed",
                "shown",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The bell has ……………………………..",
            "description": "Rung is the past participle form of ring. ",
            "answers": [
                "rang",
                "rung",
                "ringed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}